Guide to the Juan Felipe Herrera Papers, ca. 1970-1998 M1043
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 9: Accession 2011-054
  - 26) 2 Color: Twin Towers Performance rehearsal at Arte Americas. Fresno. Bryan Medina and Michael Medrano, Poets. (Sept. 11, memorial performance, directedby JFH. 2003. (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - 27) 25 Photos of Teatro Zapata. Directed by JFH. Fresno. 1992-1999 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - 28) 1 Photo of JFH. Anonymous Photog. Fresno. Late 90's (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - 29)1 Contact print of 19 images of Teatro Zapata. Fresno. Late 90's (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - 30) 1 B/W image of muscian. Panama. 1960's. By Anthropologist, Robert Alvarez. (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - 31) 1 B/W image of Margarita, Chamula Indian child. San Cristobal de las Casas. 1970. J (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - 32) 1 B/W transparency of Uncle Chente Quintana (left) with artist cadre in El Paso, Tx. 1921 (circa). (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - 33) 1 B/W print of musiscian from Zinacantan, Chiapaas. Tzotzil Tzeltal. (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - 34) 1 B/W print of Fresno Bee Photographer and friend, Hector Amezcua, Fresno. Mid 90's (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - 35) Print of JFH, 1982. San Francisco. Mission District. By Photog Wilfredo Q. Castano. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - 36)1 B/W commercial print of Mexican Actress, La Tongolele. Circa 1950's (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - 37) 2 B/W prints of Margarita Robles reading poetry at National Park Service Lecture Hall. Western Regional Office. 12th floor. San Francisco. JFH in background. Anonymous. (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - 38) 6 B/W large prints of JFH's students involved in Open-Air performance work. De Anza Community College. Cupertino, Ca. 1985. Anonymous (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - 39) 1 B/W Promo Print of original Culture Clash Latino Comedy Troupe. (Left to Right: Herbert Siquenza, Marga Gomez, Richard Montoya, Slick Ric Salinas, Jose Antonio Burciaga and Monica Palacios. Autographed to JFH and Margarita Roles. SF. 6/4/85. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - 40) 10 color images of Theatre Degree Zero (Tucson, Az) working on "Quentino" poem by JFH. Directed by John Sullivan. Early 90's. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - 41) 19 color images of Theatre Degree Zero (Tucson, Az.) working on "Quentino" poem by JFH. Directed by John Sullivan. Early 90's (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - 42) 7 color images of Theatre Degree Zero (Tuscon, Az.) working on "Voces en el umbral" by John Sullivan. Early 90's. With letter to JFH. (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - 43) 4 color images of Theatre Degree Zero (Tucson, Az.) working on "San Francisco de Asi" poem by JFH (from Akrilica). Directed by John Sullivan. Douglas, Az. Early 90's (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - 44) 32 color images of Theatre Degree Zero (Tucson, Az.) working on "Dire Moon Cartoons" Directed by John Sullivan. Early 90's. (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - 45) 2 color images of "Instant Living Murals" after the work of ASCO. Fresno, Ca. Raquel Solis, (Left) and Silvia Gonzalez (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - 46) 1 B/W print of Manikrudo Ensemble performing "Orientation Cafe". Arcata, Ca. CSU-Summer Arts. Early 90's. Written and Directed by JFH. Anonymous. (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - 47) Transparency of Madison Magazine, 12/99 Cover. (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - 48) 1 color image of Margarita Robles reading poetry. Univ. Iowa. 1988. (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - 49) 1 Promo Print of Monica Palacios. Late 90's (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - 50) 1 B/W contact sheet of Naja Village, Selva Lacandona. Chiapas, MEx. 1993. (JFH with Chan Kin Jose and Bor and with Mexican student anthropology grad. (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - 51) 1 color image of Poetry and Blues Review at Eulipia's restaurant. San Jose, Ca. Late 80's. JFH with Alex Di Prima. Theatre skit. (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - 52) 1 B/W print of JFH. Carbondale, Ill. 1993 SIU. (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - 53) 2 B/W promo print of Michele Serros, Poet. Late 90's (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - 54) 1 Promo print of Ruben Martinez, Poet. Late 90's (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - 55) 1 B/W print of El Colorin Village, Sierra Madre, Nayarit. Healing Ceremony. Print made in 1969, Fred Endsley's apartment, Santa Monica, Ca. (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - 56) Margarita Robles Promo print. Late 90's. Fresno. (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - 57) Margarita Robles promo print. By Hector Amezcua. CSU-F. late 90's. (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - 58) 29 color images of Naja's environs. Rain Forest. Chiapas, Mexico (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - 59) 26 color images of De Anza College student performance work. Directed by JFH. Cupertino. 1986 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - 60) 2 color images of Floricanto Poetry festival at Stanford University. 1989. JFH and Alurista. Anonymous (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - 61) 46 color images of Tzotzil Tzeltal Tzajalchen Pueblo protest march in San Cristobal de Las Casa, Chiapas. 1/93. (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - 62) 18 B/W images of Alicia Alonso's Ballet in rehearsal. Habana, Cuba. 1979. (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - 63) 27 images of Cultural Performance study by JFH. 24th Street. Mission District, SF. 1980 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - 64) 3 art exhibit images. Centro Cultural de la Raza. San Diego, Ca. Mid 80's. (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - 65) 3 color images of visit to Univ. of Minneapolis. With Ray Gonzalez at office and Sandra Alcosser at reading. (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - 66) 19 color images of Taos and Taos Pueblo. Reading at the Taos Poetry Circus. Early 2000's (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - 67) 1 color of Margarita Robles. San Jose Ave apartment, Mission District, 1984. (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - 68) 1 color image of Francisco Alarcon. San Jose ave apartment. 1984-5. (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - 69) 1 color images of John Marron, poet and friend. New Jersey. Anonymous. Late 90's. (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - 70) 1 b/w promo print of Jim Sagel, poet and friend. Early 90's. By Margory Denton. For CSU-F reading. (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - 71) 1 color image of Margarita Robles, George Barlow (poet) with Bobbie Barlow. Iowa City. Late 80's (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - 72) 1 color image of Margarita Robles leading a women's workshop in poetry. MACLA. San Jose, Ca. 1995 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - 73) 1 color image of Margarita Robles. Fresno. Late 90's (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - 74) 2 color images of JFH reading poetry at Jose Antonio Burciaga's apartment at Stanford University. By Justo Alarcon. Mid 80's (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - 75) 1 color image of Muralist, Victor Ochoa. San Diego, Ca. Mid 80's. (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - 76) 5 b/w images of archeological excavation of Coyolxauqui. Mexico City. 1978. (journey to mexico with Francisco Alarcon) (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - 77) 1 color image of JFH and lead actor, Edward Duepner. The Upside Down Boy Musical. NYC. 2004. (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - 78) 1 B/W image of JFH's apartment wall at 949 Capp Street, SF. 94110 #10. (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - 79) 1 color image of Francisco Alarcon's apartment #4. San Jose Ave. SF. 1985 (from bedroom into living room and kitchen. (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - 80) 1 b/w image of Yvonne Yarbro Bejarano (wife at that time) and JFH. Party scene. SF. 1979. Another image of friend. Anonymous. (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - 81) 7 B/W portraits of Teatro Zapata members - Rocio Magana, Felix Rodriguez, Soledad Martinez, Liz Alfaro. By Randy Vaughn-Dotta, CSUF Photog. (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - 82) 5 color images of Twin Towers Performance rehearsal. Arte Americas. Directed by JFH. Early 2000. (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - 83) 1 b/w print of JFH. SF. 1982. Signed by Photog, Wilfredo Q. Castano. (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - 84) 7 b/w images of Yo Puedo Students. UCSC. Summer, 1985. Anonymous. (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - 85) 2 B/W images of Manikrudo ensemble directed by JFH. Early 90's. Arcata, Ca. (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - 86) 1 color image of Manikudo ensemble directed by JFH. Late 90's. CSU-Long Beach. (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - 87) 2 color images of CSU-F JFH students preparing art for first Tamejavi Festival in Fresno, Ca. 2002? (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - 88) 1 B/W promotional image of Abraham Adzenya (Ghana Drummer) and Li-Young Lee. For Manikudro workshop. CSU-Long Beach. Late 90's. (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - 89) 1 B/W promotional image og Genny Lim for Manikrudo workshop. Late 90's (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - 90) 3 images of sons, Joaquin Herrera, and Robert Segura (younger) outside house on So. Johnson Street, Iowa City. 1989 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - 91) 1 color image of Mexican cinema comedian, Firulais (in his later years). Guadalajara, Mexico. 1978. By Francisco Alarcon. (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - 92) 1 B/W image of Florisong. Poetry Collective. workshop. San Jose. Early 80's. Margarita Robles (bottom row, center) Anonymous. (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - 93) 2 images. One of JFH daughter, Almasol, with cat in JFH studio on Folsom Street, Mission District, SF. And another of Almasol at Francisco Alarcon's apartment on San Jose ave. SF. 1982 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - 94) 1 color image of JFH in between friends, Yamillete Gutierrez (left) and Richard Delgado, right. Late 90's Sanger, CA (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - 95) 7 color images of JFH students. CSU-F. 2002? (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - 96) 3 images of Murals by Guillermo Aranda, friend. Soledad Correctional Facility, Soledad, Ca. 1987 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - 97) 17 images of Memorial for Cesar Chavez, Eduard James Olmos and public. Early 90's (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - 98) 2 B/W images of National Chicano Studies Conference in Sacramento, Ca. Francisco Alarcon (with Tenaz Tee) and William Flores. By Margarita Robles. 80's (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - 99) 2 color images of students from Jackson, Wyo. 2004. Poetry visit. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - 100) 1 color image of US-Mexico Conference Forum sponsored by the Tomas Rivera Endowment. UCR. JFH, Martinez Saldana, Cristian Flores and Michael Jaime and student in foreground. 2006. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - 101) 2 B/W images of JFH at Eulipia's in San Jose, Ca. Celebrating publication of Facegames. 1987. Margarita Robles, Photog. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - 102) 8 B/W images of SF protest against US Intervention in El Salvador. 1981. Dolores Park and Mission Street. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - 103) 12 B/W images of Poetry Reading in San Jose, Ca. Margarita Robles, Felix Alvarez and Jose Antonion Burciaga. Filmed by Ed Kissam and crew. 1984 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - 104) 2 color photos of JFH in Olympic Mtns of Seattle and Vancouver, Canada By Yvonne Yarro Bejarno. 1979. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - 105) 2 B/W images of JFH. N. 16th Street apt. San Jose. 1987. By Margarita Robles. (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - 106) 3 color images of Margarita Robles, JFH and Rita Magdaleno, poet and friend. San Antionio. NACHS conference. 10/91. (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - 107) 2 images of JFH. SF. 1984. (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - 108) 6 images of John Marron, Poet. And JFH. NYC and Highland Park NJ. Early 90's (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - 109) 5 color images: One of Dr. Elias Nandino, poet with members of Literary Workshop of Guadalajara where the Premio Nacional was given to Nandino at the Palacio Nacional. 1982. One of Nandino with writers, Sergio Pitol, Carlos Monsivais at the Palacio Nacional. 1982. One of Nandino with writers, Sergio Pitol, Carlos Monsivais at the Polifotro Siqueiros, Mexico City. 1982. And others with Justo Alarcon, Lucha Corpi, Francisco Alarcon and Luis Leal. Attended by Francisco Alarcon. Anonymous (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - 110) 2 B/W of Francisco Alarcon and Melinda Melendez (Stanford student) at NACHS conference, Sacramento. 1985 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - 111) 1 B/W of JFH in El Paso, Tx. By Margarita Robles. 1984 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - 112) 23 color images and negs of Twin Towers Performance rehearsals. Arte Americas. Fresno. Imags by JFH. 2002. James Mitchell Grant-CSUF. (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - 113) 16 color images of Mexico City. 1993 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - 114) 5 b/w images of 24th street fair. SF. 1982 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - 115) 23 images of 1985 Irvine Chicano poetry prize. Margarita Robles. JFH and Ruben Medina. (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - 116) Guillermo Gomez Pena and Jose Antonio Burciaga. Galeria de la Raza. SF. Anonymous. 9/95 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - 117) 1 color images of JFH at DC hotel before Americas Award at Library of Congress. 1999. (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - 118) 4 rare colors slides of artist Ramiro Martinez's work. Fresno. 1992 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - 119) 1 color image of JFH and Carol Koch before marriage. 1968. Los Angeles. Wilshire Blvd. At Carol's parent's apt. Westwood. (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - 120) 1 color image of JFH at Disneyland. 1975. By Lupe Duarte Chacon (partner). (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - 121) 3 color images of Habana, Cuba by Kane Shahabi, son-in-law. 2000's (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - 122) 3 color images of Salt Lake City, Utah. JFH, Late 90's. (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - 123) 1 color image of JFH and Sandra Alcosser. Poetry Reading. Minneapolis. Twin Cities. Late 90's (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - 124) 1 color image of Presentations Grants Judges. NEA office. 90's Joanne Woodward 1st row. JFH middle top row. DC. (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - 125) 1 color image of JFH in Pike Place market, Seattle, Wa. 1979. By Yvonne Yarbro Bejarano (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - 126) 1 sepia image of RCAF mural in Sacramento, Ca. 1974. Anonymous (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - 127) 1 color image of Elly Simmons, Illustrator and JFH at presentation of Calling the Doves. Galeria de la Raza. SF. 1995 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - 128) 1 b/w image of JFH performance warm ups. De Anza College, Cupertino. 1986. Anonymous. (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - 129) 1 b/w contact sheet (only remaining images). By YolandaM. Lopez. For promo of Exiles of Desire reading at Galeria de la Raza. SF. 1983. (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - 130) 1 b/w promo image of Monica Palacios. Late 90's. By Becky Villasenor. (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - 131) 1 B/W contact sheet of Margarita Robles in Santa Fe, NM. 1984. (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - 132) 3 b/w promo prints of John Marron, poet, Late 90's. Anonymous. (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - 133) 4 B/W promo prints: Arlene Biala, Victor Hernandez Cruz, Jimmy Biala on Congas and Ruben Martinez, poets. Late 90's. (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - 134) 1 color image of Shelly Silva on stage. Manikrudo ensemble. Orientation Nation Cafe performance. Arcata, Ca. early 90's. Anonymous. (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - 135) 1 color image of mural by Victor Ochoa. San Diego, Ca. undated. Anonymous. (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - 136) 14 B/W Mexico, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - 137) 1 B/W print of JFH's mother, Lucha Quintana. 1936, El Paso, Tx. Segundo Barrio. (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - 138) 20 Color prints. Galveston Elementary, Chandler, Az. 1/19/07. Author Visit. (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - 139) 3 color shots of Jim Sagel's (poet) front yard. Espanola, N.M. 1984 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - 140) 17 color prints with negs. Twin Towers Memorial performance rehearsal. Arte Americas. Fresno. 2002 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - 141) 9 B/W images of New York City. Visiting John Marron, poet, Mid-90's (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - 142) 24 prints and negs. Twin Tower Memorial rehearsal. Arte Americas. Fresno. 2002 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - 143) 26 color prints of Yo Puedo program. UCSC. JFH (teacher). 1985 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - 144) 3 color prints of Everardo Pedraza's High School class. Porterville, Ca. 2008 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - 145) 13 B/W prints of Poetry into Performance workshop for Cal State Summer Arts program. Margarita Robles, Artist in Residence. Mid-90's (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - 146) 23 color prints of Teatro Zapata in Selma. Directed by JFH. Early 2000's. (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - 147) 18 color prints of Theatre Degree Zero rehearsing "Noche Verde Neuclear," poem by JFH. Late 90's. Directed by John Sullivan. (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - 148) 16 B/W prints of Poetry into Performance Workshop. Summer Arts-CSU. Mid-90's (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - 149)15 shots of Chicano Moratorium. East Los Angeles. 8/29/80 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - 150) 66 color slides of Journey to Mexico. With rare shots of Legendary shaman, Ramon Medina Silva, Ranchito El Colorin, Sierra Madre, Nayarit. 1970. With images of Chiapas - Rain Forest (Lacanja Chan Shayab, Naja), Joigelito, San Cristobal de las Casas, San Juan Chamula. 1970 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - 151) 1 B/W print of La Diana Sculpture fountain, outside the Diana Cinema. Mexico City. 1993 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - 152) 7 color prints of Theatre Degree Zero in performance. "Quentino (poem by JFH). Nogales, Sonora. Late 90's. (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - 153) 14 color prints of Journey to Santa Fe and New Mexico with Margarita Robles. Indian Student Power Conference in Santa Fe. 6/22/1984. (Vine Deloria in image, Art show.) (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - 154) 1 B/W print of Teatro Chicano - Barrios Unidos. San Jose. 1978. (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - 155) 29 B/W prints of 1st Street Project Band - Francis Wong, Wally Schmally, Beau Kane and K.C. 1988. (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - 156) 1 color image of "Family Dinner" Villa Grande, North Ca. Friends from UCLA 1967. 1992. (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - 157) 2 color images of Conchero Danzantes blessing of Quetzalcoatl sculpture by Robert Graham, in San Jose, Ca. 90's (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - 158) 1 B/W image of JFH daughter, Almasol, at Folsom Flat, in Mission District, SF. 1982. (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - 159) 2 color shots. Alice Walker, Brian Wilson, World College West Mural inauguration of Bridge of Peace/Puente de la Paz by Juana Alicia. 9/17/88. Cecilia Brunazzi, Margarita Robles and Juana Alicia shot. (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - 160) 2 color images. Lucha Corpi, Francisco Alarcon. Acceptance of prize speech. Palabra Nueva. UTEP. 4/22/83. Anonymous. (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - 161) 1 color image of Before Columbus American Books Award winners. Ishmael Reed, Ana Castillo, Jon Wieners, Etheridge Knight, Ai, lamont Steptoe. Oakland. 1997 Anonymous. (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - 162) 1 color image of JFH and Yolanda Luera. Valencia, Ca. 1992. By Margarita Robles. (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - 163) 1 B/W of Enrique Romo. Poet Promocion Nacional. INBA. Mexico City. By Francisco Alarcon. 1978. (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - 164) 1 color image of Margarita Robles. El Paso, Tx. Huerta Street. 1984 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - 165) 2 color images of Francisco Alarcon and his brother at JFH wedding reception (Yvonne Yarboro Bejarno). Logan Heights, San Diego. 1979. (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - 166) 1 B/W OF JFH. Blue Heron Ranch. Lincoln, Ca. (owned by Olivia Mercado). By Margarita Robles. 1985 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - 167) 2 b/w images. One of JFH at St. Francis Fountain, 24th & York Street. 1981 by Victor Martinez. The other of back of Folsom Flat where JFH lived in 1982. (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - 168) 3 B/W shots of San Juan Bautista, Ca. When JFH acted in Teatro Campesino's 20th Anniversary California Tour. 1985. (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - 169) 4 B/W shots of SF Beach. 1982 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - 170) 1 B/W shot of JFH, Roberto Cantu and Salvador Rodriguez del Pino. Chicano Literature Panel. UCR. Mid 80's. Anonymous (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - 171) 2 Color shots of duplex in Carbondale, Ill. 1993. (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - 172) 1 color print of JFH accepting FOCAL award in Children's Lit. L.A. main library. Anonymous. 1996 circa (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - 173) 2 B/W images of JFH's mother's TV with Casablanca playing 1982 Folsom Street Flat. SF. (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - 174) 1 B/W image of Truck. Habana, Cuba by JFH son-in-law, Kane Shahabi. 2002. (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - 175) 13 B/W images of No Empire/Poetasumanos Mono Poem Reading at Project Artaud, Mission District. SF. Clyde Salazar, Tony Curiel, Barbara Brinson-Pineda, Yvonne Yarbro-Bejarano, Art Sato, Conyus, Merle Woo, Pedro Ramirez, Orlando Ramirez, David Volpendesta, Javier Pacheco. By Pedro Ramirez and JFH. 1982. (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - 176) 3 color prints of JFH and reception for Children's Musical - Salsalandia - written by JFH. At La Jolla Playhouse. La Jolla, Ca. 3/08 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - 177) 3 B/W images of Florisong Poetry Collective. San Jose, Ca. Margarita Robles house on Pitcairn street. 1982 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - 178) 11 color prints of JFHout-door performance experiments. De Anza College. Cupertino, Ca. 1986 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - 179) 2 color prints of Yvonne Yarbro-Bejarno on hiking trail. Seattle, Wa. 1979 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - 180) 1 color print of poetry band. Rick Sajor on congas and friend on drums. 1985. San Francisco. Intersection Space. (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - 181) 4 color shot of women at UNM Indian Student Power Conference. By Margarita Robles. (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Bonus: Mission District. S. Francisco 1982. JFH (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Box Listing (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - 1) 1 color shot of Yvonne Yarbro Bejarano interviewing a member of Teatro de la Esperanza. Point Bonita. TENAZ 11th Teatro Festival. SF. 1981 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - 2) 1 B/W photo after First Corn Ceremony (and man in shawl waiting to be healed by Ramon Medina Silva (not in picture). El Colorin Rancho. Sierra Madre. Nayarit. Mexico. 1970 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - 3) 1 color image of JFH daughter, Almasol. Folsom Street Flat. SF. 1982 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - 4) 1 color photo of downtown Juarez, Chihuahua. 1984 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - 5) 1 color print of JFH open air experiment. De Anza College. Cupertino, Ca. 1986. (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - 6) 1 color print of Poetry into Performance Workshop. CSU Summer Arts. Arcata, Ca. Margarita Robles, Genny Lim and JFH. Anonymous. (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - 7) 1 B/W SF beachfront shot. SF. 1982-3. (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - 8) 1 color print of JFH. East Village. NYC. By John Marron. Mid 90's (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - 9) 1 B/W mural inside bank in Guadalajara, Mexico. 1978 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - 10) 1 B/W image of Margarita Robles. Soho. NYC. Mid-90's (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - 11) 1 B/W of JFH in apartment. SF. 1981 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - 12) 1 B/W Yvonne Yarbro Bejarano. 11th TENAZ Chicano Teatro Conference. Point Bonita, Bay Area. 1981 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - 13) 1 color of Chicano Moratorium. LA, Whittier Blvd. 1980. (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - 14) 1 color of Francisco X. Alarcon's apartment kitchen view. San Jose Ave. SF. 1984 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - 15) 2 B/W of JFH in El Paso, Tx. Stanton Street. 1984. By Margarita Robles (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - 16) 3 8/10 B/W JFH's Open Air Performance Experiment. De Anza Community College. 1987 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - 17) 1 B/W contact sheet of JFH journey to Naja, Selva Lacandona. Chiapas, Mx. Lake Naja. With Chan K'in Mario, Chan K'in Jose (wit Backpacks), Pancho Villa (on road and sitting). 1993 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - 18) 1 B/W of 24th Street Fair. SF. Ca. (Teatro Gusto Members front row) (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - 19) 3 B/W of Journey to Cuba. One en route (Church in Zamora, Michoacan) another with Yvonne Yarbro Bejarano & Josue Lopez, Marta Menchaca, and another of group in Habana. Last one of two fiction writers holding an impromptu outside conference with us visitors from US. Camaguey, Cuba. 1979 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - 20) 1 Color of Matt Lippmann (blue), poet and friend at AWP conference in Baltimore, Md. 2005? (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - 21) 1 B/W of car outside Sagrado Corazon Church, Segundo Barrio, El Paso, Tx. 1984 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - 22) 1 Negative strip of Lake Naja with Kayum Mario. Selva Lacandona, Chiapas, Mex. 1993. Used for Cover of Mayan Drifter by JFH in 1997. (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - 23) 1 Color of JFH in Chicago for the Arts & Humanities Festival. 1999? By Margarita Robles. (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - 24) 1 B/W Point Bonita, TENAZ Festival. 1981. (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - 25) 1 Color of Rt. #1. To JFH House. Carbondale, Ill. 1993. (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - 26) 1 B/W of Manikudo Workshop led by JFH. Arcata, Ca. (CSU-Summer Arts). 1994? (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - 27) 1 B/W Promo shot of John Marron, Poet. 1997? (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - 28) 1 Color shot of Strand Theatre. West Liberty, IA. 1989. (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - 29) 1 Color of Chicano Moratorium. LA. 1980 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - 30) 1 Color of Road to San Cristobal de Las Casa, Chiapas, Mx. 1993 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - 31) 1 B/W Xmas card with fotos of Ricardo "Slic Ric" Salinas, Actor, and his children, Lola and Daisy. 2003. LA (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - 32) 1 Color of 2 teens (from Tlaxcala) from Jackson, Wyoming. 2002? (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - 33) 1 Color of Joaquin Ramon Herrera shoveling snow outside home in Iowa City, IA. 1989 (Box 4, Folder 67)